Preliminary Guide to the Rufus Lusk & Sons business and personal records, 1896-1994 MS2189
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Rufus S. Lusk & Son business and personal records
1896-1994
1930-1993
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2189
57 Linear Feet
Founded by Rufus S. Lusk, Sr.(d. 1971), Rufus S. Lusk & Son, Inc. was the leader in the Mid-Atlantic region for providing the most accurate and reliable real estate sales, ownership, and mortgage information. For nearly 70 year, the Rufus S. Lusk & Son company published real estate information products which made a significant contribution to the Washington area community. Within the collection much of the collection is related to the work of Lusk & Son, but there are also materials related to other activities for Rufus S. Lusk including the Washington Taxpayers' Association and the Washington Taxpayers' Protective Association, and the Gourmet Society Dinner Club. The material dates from the 1930s through 1994. The material in Series 3 relates to The Tri-State Commission and the Washington Metropolitan Transportation Authority (METRO). These records appear to all come from the records of Jerome M. Alper.
Arrangement
Collection remains in original order, but folder titles were organized within the finding aid and three series were created for ease of browsing the finding aid: Business records, Civic and personal records, and Transportation
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Founded by Rufus S. Lusk, Sr.(d. 1971), Rufus S. Lusk & Son, Inc. was the leader in the Mid-Atlantic region for providing the most accurate and reliable real estate sales, ownership, and mortgage information. For nearly 70 year, the Rufus S. Lusk & Son company published real estate information products which made a significant contribution to the Washington area community. While the Lusk company primarily served the real estate and financial communities through the dissemination of its information, homeowners and others interested in real estate trends used Lusk publications to keep abreast of developments. In 1997, the company was sold. In addition to his work in the real estate industry Rufus Lusk, Sr. was also involved in other aspects of Washington DC business and social society. He founded the Gourmet Dinner Society and the Washington Taxpayers' Association and served as a member of the Greater Washington Board of Trade.
The District of Columbia Real Estate Directory provides data about all realty in Washington. The Lusk company also produced three weekly publications including Real Estate Guides. This service provided records transfers of property and real estate mortgages.
Scope and Contents
The material in this collection includes business records, publications, correspondence, financial reports, memorandum, and photographs. Much of this material is related to the work of Lusk & Son, but there are also materials related to other activities for Rufus S. Lusk including the Washington Taxpayers' Association and Washington Taxpayers' Protective Association, and the Gourmet Society Dinner Club. The material dates from the 1930s through 1994. The material in Series 3 relates to The Tri-State Commission and the Washington Metropolitan Transporation Authority (METRO). These records appear to all come from the records of Jerome M. Alper.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Rufus Speake Lusk, III, September 20, 1996
Real property; Alper, Jerome M.; Rufus S. Lusk & Son; Lusk, Rufus Speake III; Lusk, Rufus S. (Rufus Speake)
- Business records, 1930-1994; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Organized into 3 subseries: Accounts receivable, Real estate business records, and Financial records.
  - Accounts receivable, 1953-1993; Series 1 Subseries 1
    For ease of browsing the files that are titled accounts receivable are intellectually grouped together in a subseries. The files in this subseries are arranged in box number order to leave some understanding of how these were originally grouped together.
    General
    These are a representative sample of transactional work by Lusk with clients.
    - Account receivable ledger cards - TSB [1/2], 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - TSB [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - D [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - D [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - G, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - I, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - J, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - K, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - Mc, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A - B [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A - B [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - N- O [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - N- O [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - I, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - J, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - K [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - K [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [1/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [2/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [3/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - K, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [1/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [2/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [3/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - M, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - P [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - P [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [1/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [2/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [3/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - E, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - F, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - O, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - P [1/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - P [2/2], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A [1/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A [2/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A [3/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - A [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [1/3], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [2/3], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - B [3/3], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - C, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - D [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - D [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - E, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - F, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - J, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - K, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - L [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - M [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - M [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - Mc, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - N, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - O, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - P [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - P [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - O, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - R [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - R [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - S [1/3], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - S [2/3], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - S [3/3], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - C [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - C [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - F, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - G, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards - H [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Account receivable ledger cards I, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards W [1/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards W [2/2], Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards X-Z, Circa 1953-1962; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards R [1/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Account receivable ledger cards R [2/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [1/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [2/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards A [1/2], Circa 1978-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards A [2/2], Circa 1978-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards M [1/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards M [2/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards E [1/3], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards E [2/3], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards E [3/3], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [1/4], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [2/4], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [3/4], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [4/4], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [1/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [2/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards D [1/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards D [2/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files R [1/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files R [2/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files R [3/3], Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files, Circa 1962-1985; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [1/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards C [2/2], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files F [1/3], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files F [2/3], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files F [3/3], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards D [1/2], Circa 1961-1980; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards D [2/2], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards W [1/2], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards W [2/2], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards Y-Z, Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files P [1/2], Circa 1964-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files P [2/2], Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files C [1/3], Circa 1963-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files C [2/3], Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files C [3/3], Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files A, Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger Control Cards [1/2], Circa 1973-1976; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger Control Cards [2/2], Circa 1962-1980; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards M [1/2], Circa 1962-1974; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      General Note
      These accounts were not identified as a group of dead files, but individual cards may be designated dead files.
    - Account receivable ledger cards M [2/2], Circa 1963-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards Mc-M [1/3], Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards Mc-M [2/3], Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards Mc-M [3/3], Circa 1962-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards M [1/2], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards M [2/2], Circa 1962-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards N, Circa 961-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [1/5], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [2/5], Circa 1962-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [3/5], Circa 1961-1983; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [4/5], Circa 1962-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Account receivable ledger cards S [5/5], Circa 1961-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files T [1/4], Circa 1965-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files T [2/4], Circa 1962-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files T [3/4], Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Account receivable ledger cards dead files T [4/4], Circa 1963-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Account receivable ledger cards V, Circa 1962-1982; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Accounts receivable aging report Branch #3 and "D" Nantz, 1993 February - April; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Accounts receivable aging report Branch #3 and "D" Nantz, 1993 May - July; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Real estate business records, 1930-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2
    For ease of browsing the files with real estate business records as the topic have been intellectually grouped together in this subseries. The files in this subseries are arranged in original order by box number.
    - Assessment data, 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Assessment data, 1985-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Security Bank credi line, 1981-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appraisal report, 1971; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Appraisal Davidge & Co., 1971 November; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Appraisal H.W. Robinson, 1971 November; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Apartment Directory - Virginia, 1979-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Areas: Nassau Co - NY, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Archives, 1987-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Areas: N. Mexico, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Areas: Northern Virginia, West Virginia, and Pennylvania, 1967-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Assessment Directory Arlington County, 1987-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Assessment data, 1985-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Assessment directories, 1980-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Art form, 1986-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Areas: E-H, 1972-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Areas: Virginia and West Virginia, 1986-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Assessment data: Baltimore County, 1986-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Assessment data: Calvert and Carroll Counties [1/2], 1987-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Assessment data: Calvert and Carroll Counties [2/2], 1987-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Assessment for counties C-K, 1989-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Assessement Directory: Montgomery County [1/2], 1981-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Assessement Directory: Montgomery County [2/2], 1981-1986; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Assessment Directory: Prince George's County, 1987-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Assessment Data: Prince George's County, 1985-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Assessment Data: St. Mary's and Washington Counties, 1988-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore directory survey, 1984 June; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore Office [1/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Baltimore Office [2/2], 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bookkeeping, 1979-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Brochure negatives, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - BUGS A-PG, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Builders reports and new additions, 1984 February; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Business Review of Washington, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - By-laws, 1957-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)